Tran, Le Anh (1996)

"Once the WHY is clear, the HOW goes easy"

Seoul, South Korea tranleanh.nt@gmail.com

tranleanh.github.io in /in/tranleanh

ABOUT ME -

I completed my PhD in early 2024, marking an important milestone in my research journey. I specialize in **Python** programming and have experience with various frameworks such as tensorflow, pytorch, conda, etc. My publications have mainly revolved around image enhancement, cluster analysis, and object detection. I am also a writer for popular Medium publications such as Towards Data Science, Level Up Coding, etc.

EDUCATION -

3/2021 - 2/2024 PhD in Computer Vision

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

3/2019 - 2/2021 **MSc in Computer Vision**

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

BEng in Automation and Control Engineering (graduated with honors) 9/2014 - 8/2018

HCMC University of Technology and Education (HCMUTE), Vietnam

EXPERIENCE -

4/2020 - Present Research Staff Member

MindinTech, Inc., Seoul, South Korea

Researching and developing vision-based techniques for advanced driver-assistance systems

Research Assistant 3/2021 - 2/2024

Intelligent Computing Research Lab (ICRL), Myongji University, South Korea

Researched and developed cutting-edge algorithms for image enhancement and cluster analysis

Software Development Intern 7/2019 - 9/2019

OCST Co., Ltd., Seoul, South Korea

Developed a software system for object detection streaming and data management

3/2018 - 2/2019 Al Engineer

FPT Software, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Developed and implemented vision-based algorithms for the first piloted driver-less car in Vietnam

2/2017 - 1/2018 **Teaching Assistant**

Faculty of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, HCMUTE, Vietnam

Assisted the lecturer during classes, prepared lesson plans, and evaluated assignments

EXPERTISE

Skills

- Programming: Python, Conda, Darknet, Tensorflow, Keras, Pytorch
- Document Presentation: MS Word, MS PowerPoint, LaTeX
- Technical: Statistical Analysis, Visualization, Technical Reporting, Problem Solving, etc.
- Concept: Knowledge Distillation, Knowledge Transfer, Learning without Forgetting, Dark Channel Prior, Non-Maximum Suppression, Vision Transformer, Generative Adversarial Networks, etc.

Languages

- Vietnamese (native)
- English (proficient)

Activities

- IEEE Member
- IEEE Young Professional
- Journal Reviewer: Transactions on Image Processing (IEEE), Transactions on Intelligent Transportation Systems (IEEE), Intelligent Data Analysis (IOS Press)

PUBLICATIONS	
2024	POCS-based Image Compression: An Empirical Examination TD Do $^{\nabla}$, LA Tran $^{\nabla}$, TD Nguyen, NN Truong, DC Park, MH Le
	IEEE International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD)
2024	Encoder-Decoder Networks with Guided Transmission Map for Effective Image Dehazing
	LA Tran, DC Park The Visual Computer, Springer (SCIE)
2024	Cluster Analysis via Projection onto Convex Sets
2024	LA Tran, D Kwon, HM Deberneh, DC Park
	Intelligent Data Analysis, IOS Press (SCIE)
2024	Toward Improving Robustness of Object Detectors against Domain Shift LA $Tran^{\nabla}$, NC $Tran^{\nabla}$, DC Park, J Carrabina, D Castells-Rufas
	IEEE International Conference on Green Energy, Computing and Sustainable Technology (GECOST)
2024	Single Image Dehazing via Regional Saturation-Value Translation
	LA Tran, D Kwon, DC Park Procedia Computer Science, Vol. 237
2023	Embedding Clustering via Autoencoder and Projection onto Convex Set
2023	LA Tran, TD Nguyen, TD Do, NC Tran, D Kwon, DC Park
	IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2023	Efficient Infrared-Thermal Imaging Fusion for Human Detection in Heavy Smoke Scenarios NN Truong, MH Le, TD Do, LA Tran, TD Nguyen, HH Trinh
	IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2023	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Robustness and Applicability
	LA Tran, DC Park Smart Innovation, Systems and Technologies, Vol. 333
2022	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Architecture
2022	LA Tran, DC Park
	International Conference on Advances in Signal Processing and Artificial Intelligence (ASPAI)
2022	POCS-based Clustering Algorithm LA Tran, HM Deberneh, TD Do, TD Nguyen, MH Le, DC Park
	IEEE International Workshop on Intelligent Systems (IWIS)
2022	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map for Image Dehazing
	LA Tran, S Moon, DC Park Procedia Computer Science, Vol. 204
2021	Enhancement of Robustness in Object Detection Module for ADAS
	LA Tran, TD Do, DC Park, MH Le IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2222	,
2020	Object Detection Streaming and Data Management on Web Browser LA Tran
	Technical Report, OCST Co., Ltd.
2019	Robust U-Net-based Road Lane Markings Detection for Autonomous Driving LA Tran, MH Le
	IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2018	A Vision-based Method for Autonomous Landing on a Target with a Quadcopter
	LA Tran, NP Le, TD Do, MH Le IEEE International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD)
Lindor Doviovy	
Under Review	Efficient Big Data Analysis via POCS and Centroid Neural Network LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Distilled Pooling Transformer Encoder for Efficient Realistic Image Dehazing
	LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Haze Removal via Regional Saturation-Value Translation and Soft Segmentation

LA Tran, DC Park

Soft Knowledge-based Distilled Dehazing Networks LA Tran, DC Park Under Review

Clustering Optimization via Centroid Neural Network Ensemble NC Tran $^{\nabla}$, LA Tran $^{\nabla}$, DC Park, J Carrabina, D Castells-Rufas Under Review

 $\nabla\!\!:$ equal contribution